{"data":[{"question":"To see the Statue of Liberty and taking pictures from the top of the Empire State Building are two reasons for visiting New York City.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"taking","b":"from","c":"are","d":"visiting","answer":"1","explain":" - Taking-> to take","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"40","type":"1"},{"question":"There are twenty species of wild roses in North America, all of which have prickly stems, pinnate leaves, and large flowers, which usually smell sweetly.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"are","b":"all of","c":"have","d":"sweetly","answer":"4","explain":" - Sweetly-> sweet","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"40","type":"1"},{"question":"Having chose the topics for their essays, the students were instructed to make either a preliminary outline or a rough draft.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"Having chose","b":"for","c":"the students","d":"either","answer":"1","explain":" - Having chose-> having chosen","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"40","type":"1"},{"question":"Factoring is the process of finding two or more expressions whose product is equal as the given expression.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"is","b":"finding","c":"whose","d":"as","answer":"4","explain":" - As-> to","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"40","type":"1"},{"question":"Grandma Moses having been able to continue farming, she might never have begun to paint.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"having been able","b":"to continue","c":"might never have begun","d":"to paint","answer":"1","explain":" - Havign been able to continue-> had been able","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"40","type":"1"},{"question":"Since infection can cause both fever as well as pain, it is a good idea to check a patient's temperature.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"Since","b":"can cause","c":"as well as","d":"to check","answer":"3","explain":" - As well as->and","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"40","type":"1"},{"question":"Schizophrenia, a behavioral disorder typified by a fundamental break with reality, may be triggered by genetic predisposition, stressful, drugs, or infections.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"typified","b":"with","c":"may be triggered","d":"stressful","answer":"4","explain":" - Stressful-> stress","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"40","type":"1"},{"question":"They asked us, Henry and I, whether we thought that the statistics had been presented fairly and accurately.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"Henry and I","b":"thought","c":"had been presented","d":"accurately","answer":"1","explain":" - Henry and I-> Henry and me","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"40","type":"1"},{"question":"In purchasing a winter coat, it is very important for trying it on with heavy clothing underneath.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"In","b":"for trying","c":"on","d":"underneath","answer":"4","explain":" - Underneath-> under\n\nUnder is nearly always used as a preposition (followed by a noun).\nUnderneath has a similar meaning to under, and is used especially when something is hidden or covered","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"40","type":"1"},{"question":"What happened in New York were a reaction from city workers, including firemen and policemen who had been laid off from their jobs.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"happened","b":"were","c":"including","d":"had been laid","answer":"2","explain":" - Were-> was","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"40","type":"1"}]}